...at the time of your birth
somehow affects your personality.
(Penny:)Participate in the what?
(Leonard:)I think what Sheldon's trying to say...
(Leonard:)...is that Sagittarius wouldn't have been
our first guess.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, a lot of people
think I'm a water sign.
(Penny:)Okay, let's see, what else?
(Penny:)Oh, I'm a vegetarian.
No, except for fish,
and the occasional steak. I love steak.
Well, that's interesting.
(Sheldon:)Leonard can't process corn.
So do you have some sort of a job?
PENNY:
Oh, yeah.
(Penny:)I'm a waitress
at The Cheesecake Factory.
(Leonard:)I love cheesecake.
- You're lactose intolerant.
- I don't eat it, I think it's a good idea.
(Penny:)Anyways, I'm also writing a screenplay.
(Penny:)It's about this sensitive girl who comes
to L.A. from Lincoln, Nebraska...
(Penny:)...to be an actress and winds up
a waitress at The Cheesecake Factory.
(Leonard:)So it's based on your life.
(Penny:)No, I'm from Omaha.